Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[voice] Venu al rao. Kal-El!
[Clark groans]
What happened?
Where are we?
What have you done to him?
[Chief Steward]
We have made him
what he was meant to be.
Why have you returned to us
in your failure. Kal-El?
You sent me those visions.
You called me here
to get my powers back.
We did not call you here.
Power belongs to conquerors.
All you have shown us
is weakness.
Brainiac.
Yes.
But we are not the mad. twisted
creature you met on Kandor.
We are the Brainiac
of old Krypton. uncorrupted.
And we can
give you what you seek.
You can restore my powers?
We can and we desire to.
But first. you must become
what you were meant to be.
You must show us
you are a conqueror.
Conqueror?
Hurting people
doesn't make you strong.
And losing your power.
your noble birthright
to a mere human?
Is that what strength
looks like. Kal-El?
Do you want these powers
or do you not?
What do I have to do?
You have to learn
what strength is.
[tribal drumming]
What?
What is this?
[Chief Steward] This is
what you came for. Kal-El.
Prove to us here
in Krypton's ancient past
that you are worthy
of our power.
and we will make you
strong again.
How's Kara?
She's alive.
but she needs real help.
I. I don't know what to do.
Hey. where's Dad?
Clark? He...
[Waller] Lane.
I'm taking command
of these new Kryptonian assets.
Assets?
They're barely
more than children.
There's a monster on the loose.
It defeated Supergirl.
It's impervious to Kryptonite.
And no one knows
when it's coming back.
But when it does. I need
your little scout troop
taking orders from Uncle Sam.
The kids aren't soldiers.
We're living in a post
Superman world. Lane.
Catch up.
No one is coming to save us.
[sighs wearily]
Supergirl needs an infirmary.
I'll go see about a medic.
Get those assets in line.
I need soldiers.
[growls]
[Clark] Where are we?
[Chief Steward] Where you will
prove your strength.
Your people were once
as you are now.
Primitive. weak. flightless.
But when invaders
from the stars attacked
your ancient ancestors.
the first Kryptonians
conquered them
with no more power
than you have now.
They took from their enemy
the secrets
of strength. of flight.
They turned
their dying star into Rao.
the living sun
whose offspring powers
your fortress even now.
They became Krypton.
Why are you telling me all this?
Because those invaders
are coming. Kal-El.
This very night.
And you will face them.
What?
Conquer the invaders!
Show us that you have that
ancient strength within you.
and we will restore your power.
But this isn't real. is it?
[Chief Steward] Your foes
will be as real as you are.
If you let them kill you.
you will perish.
Wait. I...
[softly] I don't want to
hurt anyone.
[intense music playing]
The invaders.
[somber music playing]
Okay. Clark's not here but
you can do this on your own.
They're your kids.
Great news!
I've spoken with Director Waller
and we've got a new plan
to stop Eradicator.
save the future.
and get you two home.
Let me guess. The plan
is for us to risk our lives
fighting that monster again
while you watch?
I do...
Look. the plan is
for everyone to do their part.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. and.
and how does dad feel
about this plan?
Come to think of it.
where is he?
Your father's found a way
to recover his powers.
He's gone to look for them.
But he'll be back!
We're never enough for you. huh?
In every single timeline
your plan is just.
"bring back Dad."
Lara. let's get out of here.
Maybe we should hear Mom out.
Ugh! You always take her side.
She's not even our real mom!
Why listen to her?
Maybe you should listen to her
because your last plan
to murder Lex Luthor
created
an uncontrollable monster
that beat Kara unconscious
before disappearing
into the time stream!
Maybe that's why. Jonathan!
Sorry for saving your life. Mom.
I guess I can't
do anything right.
Jonathan... Wait!
I... I... I... I didn't mean...
Jonathan's always like this.
Yeah. because
I made him that way.
Okay. let's get a look
at these invaders.
[metal groaning]
Oh. boy. Halt!
My warriors have you surrounded.
Surrender or...
Uh... Oh. no!
[grunts]
[speaking Coluan]
Jo p'raa horvat!
Ah!
[grunts]
[intense music playing]
[Alien Leader] Ah-ha!
[Clark grunts]
[Clark straining]
[intense music playing]
[both grunting]
[Clark panting]
[Clark grunts]
[panting]
-What?
-[speaking Coluan] En de Mat!
[both scream]
Okay. Clark's still gone.
Jon has disappeared.
and a time traveling monster
is coming to kill us.
Which of those problems
would you tackle first?
Wait. aren't you
supposed to know?
I thought I did
before I ruined everything
and chased your brother away.
I can't make this
kind of decision.
I'll screw it up.
Lara. this is your life.
Whether we work
with Waller or not.
you have to have a say in this.
We can figure it out together
but we can't do that
unless you trust yourself.
Here.
Trust yourself.
Look at that.
[Lois] What?
How do you have...
You gave me the same pep talk
before I left on this mission.
And almost the same compass.
Future Lois. your mom.
she said the same things I did?
[Lara laughs]
Pretty much.
But with more stuff about
how you and Grandpa
never got along.
[laughs]
Well. Dad and I
are too much alike.
Huh.
You know
who could use a hot dog?
[groans]
[shouts] No!
[panting]
I...
I lost.
Jimmy Flamebird?
[gasps]
Kara. you're okay!
This is great!
I am indeed conscious. Hah.
What a coincidence
that. uh. you would be here
when I woke up.
He's been here the whole time.
Why did you not leave the tent?
Because you were here.
And I'm not gonna
leave you alone again.
[stomach growling]
Oh! Thank you. Lois Lane.
Anytime.
How recovered do you feel?
Oh. I am ready to fight.
Great! Great.
Uh. how about
instead of fighting.
you go have a word with Jon?
Are you unable to parent him
yourself. Lois Lane?
That's...
That's exactly it. actually.
Um. I can't do this all alone.
And is Kal-El
unable to assist you?
[intense music playing]
[Clark groans]
[mumbling]
[Chief Steward] Be still.
I gotta stop
waking up like this.
[metal groans]
[Alien Leader groaning]
[grunts]
[sighs wearily]
[growls]
[speaking Coluan]
En de mat. Huzar!
Wait. wait. wait. wait!
Ah!
[exclaims]
[Clark] Just listen.
[grunts]
[both shout]
[growls]
What was I...
[Alien Leader panting]
Your arm.
[whimpering]
[Clark grunts] Hold still. Ugh!
[Alien Leader panting]
No more fighting.
I am your friend.
Friend.
Fuh...
Fuh... rend.
[bang]
[grunts]
Hello. Jonathan Lane.
Are you playing moon catch?
Leave me alone.
It is better to talk
than to run.
You will not be
able to escape me.
What do you want?
I want to know
why you're on the moon
and why you are angry at me.
who saved your life?
I'm not angry at you.
Aunt Kara. I just...
I went off mission.
I let Lara leave by herself.
I let Eradicator escape.
I tried this before. I failed.
I'm failing again.
and that's why
everyone always wishes
I was my perfect dad.
because who wants me?
You are mistaken.
Your father is not perfect.
Lois Lane and the others
imagine that he is perfect
because even in failure.
he will not give up on them.
And I will not give up on you.
They need us.
Jonathan!
You came back.
Jonathan has returned
to help us
defeat the Eradicator.
I won't take orders
from you or Amanda Waller.
And I'll prove to you
that I can do this myself!
Mm! I'm just glad you're back.
Hope your little super teens
are ready for a fight.
Lex has found
a temporal anomaly.
Time travel.
[intense music playing]
Whoa. I got you. buddy.
You need to rest.
[suspenseful music playing]
We'll get you back to your ship.
I need to get home
to my people. too.
[growling]
Look out!
Aah!
[Clark] No!
[beast growling]
[Clark grunts]
[panting]
[grunts]
[Clark straining]
I can't die here.
Aah!
[intense music playing]
[beast growls]
Aah!
[panting]
What's happening to me?
[Alien Leader gasping]
Oh. no. No. no.
Stay with me. buddy.
[Clark] We can make it home.
We have to.
[buzzes]
[Waller] This
is the site of Zero Day.
the first alien attack
on American soil.
It's now area zero.
a Checkmate Command Post.
And Eradicator is coming here?
Unless Luthor
is wasting all our time.
The data doesn't lie.
Something is coming.
And we have less than 48 hours
to prepare for it.
[Waller] This operation.
codenamed "Doomsday".
will have two lines of defense.
The first line will be
the superhumans
led by Agent Wilson.
Kryptonians fall in.
Jonathan and Lara will fight.
but they'll take their orders
from Supergirl.
Who decided this?
-[Supergirl] We did.
-Together.
Is there a problem?
Of course not.
Glad to have you.
Let's hope you're as super
as you think you are.
[engines rumbling]
[all grunting]
[hissing]
[grunts]
[scoffs] Are you really
running away again?
I know when to get off
a sinking ship.
What? This is your ship!
You have to face the problems
you created!
Me? The Kryptonians did this.
You made the monster!
You set it free!
What am I supposed to do?
Just let the aliens
rule over us?
I get why you're scared.
I'm human. too.
But those aliens have been
paying for your mistakes. Lex.
It's time to act like
the hero you pretend to be.
Or admit that
you're the villain.
[intense music playing]
[Clark panting]
[grunts]
Huh?
[speaking Coluan] Choprra.
Lot'zar memu shin!
Lot'zar!
I'm not here to fight.
Wah hu shah.
Please. your friend needs help.
[baby crying]
You people aren't invaders.
You're refugees!
Wait! No. Please.
I don't want to hurt you.
Don't!
I have to get home.
[grunts]
[gasps]
Don't make me do this.
[growls]
[Chief Steward] Do it!
No.
They already died once.
What's the harm
in killing them again?
Show us your strength.
[Clark grunting]
Yes!
No!
[muttering in Coluan]
I won't murder these people
just to satisfy you.
That's not what strength is.
Then you will perish here.
And your family's hope
will die with you.
[Alien Leader] Hevar.
[speaking Coluan]
Or'e mak du hevar.
[Chief Steward] No.
Thank you.
[Chief Steward] No!
Enough. Brainiac.
I've won your game.
We offer you power.
and you reject it?
You can perish in your weakness.
[somber music playing]
Where is Luthor?
I'm here. Director Waller.
[sparking]
[bang]
[intense music playing]
[eerie music playing]
[Eradicator chuckles]
You were expecting me.
I am the being
you call Eradicator.
and I am here...
[Jonathan grunts]
[all gasp]
I told you I'd do it.
We don't need anyone
to come save us.
[growls]
Like I said. I am Superman.
I...
[grunts]
[bang]
Jonathan!
Fools.
You have no Superman
to defend you.
And I'm here to make sure
you never do.
[Clark] Your invaders.
they called me something
there at the end.
What was it?
[Chief Steward]
They called you friend.
And that Kal-El
is why you failed.
I defeated their leader.
I won them over...
I sent you to dominate the
Coluans. not befriend them.
It is their fate to serve you.
As it is always the fate of
the weak to serve the strong.
The entire trajectory
of the Empire
is built on
that one just principle.
And where did that
trajectory end?
Where's your Empire now?
We will not be questioned
by a beggar.
[struggling]
If the weak do not
serve the strong.
then what is the order
of the universe?
What is the purpose
of our sacrifice?
How have we spent
these last 10.0000 years?
You...
You're the one
I carried up the mountain.
Yes.
We are the eternal servant
of the Empire.
But what they did to you...
I'm so sorry.
Enough!
You insult
our millennia of service
with your pretense of mercy.
and you will die for it.
[Clark] I have to get back
to my family.
-We tried to teach you. Kal-El.
-[grunting]
There can be no compromise.
Only weakness and strength.
[Bizarro] Die!
[screaming]
[closing theme music playing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today